{
    "subject": "resource/East_Germany",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/East_German_mark",
    "human_readable": "The currency of East Germany was the East German mark.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9687241911888123,
            "question": "Was the East German mark a common currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9591398239135742,
            "question": "What was the currency of East Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8350549340248108,
            "question": "Can you exchange East German marks for other currencies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8071951270103455,
            "question": "How did the value of the East German mark compare to other currencies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7998228669166565,
            "question": "What was the economic situation in East Germany during its use of the East German mark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7532070279121399,
            "question": "What denomination was used in East Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6340723037719727,
            "question": "Did the East German mark have a historical impact?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6231465339660645,
            "question": "Is the East German mark still in use today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6065024137496948,
            "question": "Were there any special features on East German banknotes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41179990768432617,
            "question": "What replaced the East German mark after reunification?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of East Germany was the East German mark.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8965_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any special features on East German banknotes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8965_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the East German mark still in use today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8965_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did the East German mark have a historical impact?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8965_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8965_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8965_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8965_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8965_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8965_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8965_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8965_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8965_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8965_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8965_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide information about the currency in East Germany, stating that the official currency is the East German mark ( Ostmark or GDR mark) and that it was replaced by the West German Deutschmark at a fixed exchange rate of 1:1 for most transactions. This supports the statement that the currency of East Germany was indeed the East German mark."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The currency of East Germany was the East German mark.\" For example, document `46.txt` mentions the \"Eastern Mark or Ostmark,\" and `26.txt` refers to it as the \"East German mark\" or \"GDR mark,\" confirming its use in East Germany."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}